hello my name is in Japan sparse and in
this video series we're going to go over
how you can use the redox library what's
right Jas redux estate management
library that is gaining a lot of
traction and they react community but
luckily and is not specifically tied to
react
we can use it with right chest with
relative ease will cover using redux and
rights as together here but for much
more detailed look at redux itself you
can't beat the videos that redux is
creator Dan a remote if you're not
familiar with right say yes yet you
might want to check out my previous
videos to get started in this video
well covered getting redux installed
configuring the Reebok store using the
story to get state into rage as
components and the videos to follow will
cover dispatching actions handling those
actions through reducer putting it all
together to update right based on
actions in other tax let's get started
with these examples were gonna pick up
where we left off in the riot with
Westpac introduction in order to use
redux we're gonna need to install that
module so I'm going to start running an
MPN in scale safe redux and now that we
have the redox module installed to use
our and p.m. script to run with tax debt
server
taking NPM err on death
we look at the browser and refresh just
to make sure pages still being served by
text ad server everything checks out so
we're ready to get started
so it's redux and starred first thing
we're gonna do is we're going to create
a reference to it in our index JSP file
gonna add bar redux equals require redux
that's gonna pull the redox library into
our file and now that we have redux
next thing we need to do is create a
producer function so no adverse producer
to set it equal function that takes two
arguments the first one its state the
second one is action producer needs to
always return a state so for now we're
just gonna turn the state that's past 10
so make no modifications will return in
new objects just pass it right on
through because we're running web pack
with Babel we can use a mere six sorry
yes 2015 cent tax so I can set a default
value to state right inside the
arguments for the function so I said
that's equal an object and we're gonna
give it a title properly with a default
value of default title now that we have
the reducer we can use that create a
store and the store is basically going
to contain our state for application so
to do that will cause increased or
method on the redox object and more sign
its value back into redux
store gonna take my document I add event
listener line I'm just gonna break that
down into multiple lines that we have
some room to work and I want to take
this redux store object that I just
created a pass it into my sample output
tag gonna do that by passing an object
and I'm gonna sign a store property on
that object the value of redox store now
we're taking that story that redux
created with a reducer we're passing
into our rights so that we can use it
now they're passing that in there let's
go into our sample output that tag file
and make some changes to replace the
title with a call to this dot dot store
and that's gonna give us that redox
store object that we just passed and and
the store object has a get state method
on it that allows us to get access to
the state returning former reducer and
because that state has a title property
we can call that
and that should assign the h1 value to
the title that we pass back from her
state we look at index NJS that is the
value to fall title and since we're
running backs dead server it's been
rebuilding with each change so we should
be able to go into a browser refresh and
see this state
turning that default title value and our
tag is using it just bypassing the story
in to tack we haven't done anything
super exciting at this point but we have
laid the groundwork and we know that we
have a Redux or producer and our tags
all connected wired up properly so next
time we can build on that we can start
introducing the concept of actions thank
you for watching hope you found this
video helpful and be sure to keep an eye
out for the next video in the series